# THIBAUT SCHLICK

Email: <a href="mailto:thibaut.schlick@gmail.com">thibaut.schlick@gmail.com</a> ♦ Github:luffy78dev ♦ <a href="http://thibaut-dev-web.com">http://thibaut-dev-web.com</a> Phone: 437 213 8822 ♦ Adress: 21 Widmer Street, Toronto ON M5V 0B8

# WEB DEVELOPER

Dedicated and self-motivated professional with two years of successful experience consulting on multifaceted projects, designing and integrating comprehensive and functional websites, and facilitating positive relationships with a wide range of clients, colleagues, and key business partners. Consistently recognized for contributions and reputation for resolving complex technical issues. Commended for organization, efficiency, priority management, and communication skills. Computer savvy and familiar with many modern systems, software applications, and webbased technologies.

#### Technical Proficiencies:

HTML5 ♦ CSS3 ♦ PHP5 ♦ SQL ♦ MySQL ♦ MariaDB ♦ XML ♦ AJAX ♦ JSON ♦ Bootstrap ♦ JavaScript ♦ jQuery ♦ AngularJS

- ♦ Riot Js ♦ Node.js ♦ Symfony 2 ♦ Illustrator ♦ Photoshop ♦ Eclipse ♦ phpMyAdmin ♦ Git Bash ♦ Agile Scrum
- ♦ Linux ♦ English

#### INTERESTS & EXPERTISE

- Website Development
- Programming Languages
- Database Management
- Technology Integration
- End-User Interface
- Layout & Functionality

- Coding & Web Design
- Hardware & Software
- Data Entry & Analysis
- Records Reporting
- Accounting & Finance
- Planning & Scheduling

- Content Development
- Web Applications
- Project Management
- Strategic Operations
- Quality Assurance
- Performance Tracking

#### RECENT WORK EXPERIENCE

## Butterfly - Paris, France 5/2017-01/2019

Web Developer

Coordinated various aspects of web development for the communication agency Butterfly. Managed website databases with phpMyAdmin. Integrated and oversaw share ownership plans of French companies websites listed on the stock exchange under PHP5. Includes coding in JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap. Created video presentation modules of share ownership plans for employees utilizing Storyline 3. Creation and design of images with Illustrator and Photoshop.

### Axis Technologies - Paris, France

1/2017-4/2017

Web Developer

Responsible for the design, development, and integration of the company website as well as other customer sites. Helped to implement accounting software for works councils and associations using AngularJS framework and Node.js Includes coding in JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap. Code management under GitHub. Efficiently managed and organized databases using MariaDB.

#### PREVIOUS WORK EXPERIENCE

## SGSS (Societe General) - Paris, France

2015-2016

UCITS Accountant

## CACEIS (Credit Adricole) - Paris, France

2014-2015

**UCITS** Accountant

#### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

- Web Developer Certificate, Full-Stack AJC Paris Training Center (2016)
- Web Developer Certificate of Achievement OpenClassrooms.com (2015/2016)
- Master's degree, Management Control University of Nanterre (2012)